<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alpha Church</title>
    <link>http://arjetton.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alpha Church</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://arjetton.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://arjetton.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arjetton.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>What To Expect We desire to worship God in spirit and in truth (John 4:24). It is our desire to speak the truth of God in its entirety. As the apostle Peter said in 1 Peter 4:11, &amp;ldquo;If anyone speaks, he should do it as one speaking the very words of God.&amp;rdquo;
Singing Just like the first century Christians we read about in the Bible, we will sing psalms, hymns and spiritual songs (Eph 5:19).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 Update</title>
      <link>http://arjetton.github.io/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arjetton.github.io/covid/</guid>
      <description>For the safety of our church family and our community, we are complying with local orders not to gather in large groups. We hope to be back together soon. In the meantime, we are gathering online.
We are live-streaming the weekly sermon on our YouTube channel at 10am Central on Sundays. Previous sermons are also available there. For Bible study, we are meeting on Zoom. Please contact us for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lord&#39;s Supper</title>
      <link>http://arjetton.github.io/lordssupper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arjetton.github.io/lordssupper/</guid>
      <description>Preparing the Lord&amp;rsquo;s supper in 2020          January Angie   February Laura P.   March Pat   April Susan E.   May Marion &amp;amp; Lyna   June Karen   July Sharon R.   August Anna &amp;amp; Margaret   September Dianna &amp;amp; Ashlyn   October Laura P.   November Jen &amp;amp; Cathy   December Rebecca &amp;amp; Samantha    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Leadership</title>
      <link>http://arjetton.github.io/leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arjetton.github.io/leaders/</guid>
      <description>Our Elders The role of an elder is to shepherd, lead the local congregation and help ensure the work and members are acting in accordance to the teachings of Christ given through Scripture (I Tim 3:1-7, I Tim 5:17-20, Titus 1:5-9) so they are ready when the Chief Shpeherd returns (1 Peter 5:1-4). Elders are appointed over every local congregation (Acts 14:23, Titus 1:5) and oversee the church among them (1 Peter 5:2).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsibilities</title>
      <link>http://arjetton.github.io/responsibilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arjetton.github.io/responsibilities/</guid>
      <description>For the Month         Assignment responsibilities: Frechmann   Announcements: C. Ashton   Collection (count and post): J. Brinkley &amp;amp; Cann    Greeters/Visitor Card Pickup    Week of: MAR 1, 2020 MAR 8, 2020 MAR 15, 2020 MAR 22, 2020 MAR 29, 2020     East door D. Ashton K. Copeland Cann Elam T. Hill   West door T.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>